salutations and welcome to my cottage
this week i wish to share with you a
quiet early autumn day in my home
i haven't had a slow day in a while my
job has kept me busy
so it feels good to take a moment step
away from the noise
and submerge myself in a day of
homemaking
i will be baking a variety of sweet
treats
inspired by the harvest as well as
making some very luxurious
vanilla extract also at the end of this
video i will be answering a few more
questions that you've been asking
so stay tuned
[Music]
do
there is something crisp and enticing
about the harvest
and while it is only just in its infancy
over here
i'm relishing the little hints of autumn
in the air
i'm anticipating the first frost the way
it magnifies the scent of the pine
needles
with that comes a welcoming feeling that
i can't quite put into words
as if the earth is reaching out and
asking you to follow its rhythm
to prepare for the cold to take care of
your body and mind
so that you may rise up again renewed
ready for another year of beginnings
and possibilities
[Music]
so
i have an abundant tomato harvest this
year
so i am going ahead and dehydrating the
ones i know i won't be able to eat
before they spoil
they are very useful when adding to
soups and stews in the wintertime
one of my favorite things about the
harvest is the abundance of squash
i'm currently growing butternut and last
year
i grew many delicatas
[Music]
do not mistake this for a particularly
healthy meal
it is definitely a dessert but what can
i say
i have a sweet tooth
[Music]
since no one asked i thought i'd share
that
i have the strange hobby of making
miniature furniture and rooms
for what purpose i'm not sure maybe it's
for
the fairies
[Music]
so
do
[Music]
so
firstly i want to say thanks for all the
beautiful
and amazing comments that i've been
reading on my videos recently
though my channel has grown so suddenly
that
i'm not able to respond to every comment
know that i do read them
and i love to see all the kindness and
insight that people are sharing
so in response to all those questions on
how do i live this way i want to say
that
these videos help me feel calm and
centered
and peaceful they remind me to be in the
present
because i often fail at practicing that
own philosophy
i think many of us struggle when our
lives are busy
and there's a lot on our mind even
though i am so far from perfect
i keep practicing mindfulness and
being in the present and i always try to
center myself
when i see that my worries or thoughts
are getting away from me
every day i improve just a little bit
and i think that's enough
however i want to reiterate that my
videos aren't
a realistic portrayal of my daily life
i am an artist and i like to see
things through the eye of an artist i
don't always want to portray things
exactly as they are
but how they could be i do live here and
i love where i live
i love to make crafts and bake and spend
time with my pets and paint and go on
walks
all these things are true but i also
have a job i have a boyfriend
i have family and my mother lives next
door and i spend so much time with her
it's not
even funny there are so many moments
living here
where i become overwhelmed i worry i am
anxious
about anything and everything even in
the middle of nowhere
you cannot outrun your humanity last but
not least thank you to
everyone who has supported me through my
etsy shop recently
it means the world it is such a
wonderful
support to have and it is so encouraging
for a crafter and artist like myself i
will have new things available in the
coming months
it is just the best feeling ever so
thank you all for your kind inquiries
and questions
and compliments and since i've gotten so
many questions recently
i thought i would ask one to all of you
and that is what is some way that you
spread kindness
in your daily life i think there will be
a lot of creative
responses to that and i am interested to
know what brings you joy
and what helps you give joy to other
people
sending love and light to you and i will
see you all
next week bye